{
    "subject": "resource/Percy_the_Small_Engine",
    "predicate": "ontology/voice",
    "object": "resource/Linda_Ballantyne",
    "human_readable": "Percy the Small Engine is voiced by Linda Ballantyne.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9365729689598083,
            "question": "Who voices Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7979763746261597,
            "question": "Is Percy the Small Engine a fictional character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6841983199119568,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Percy the Small Engine's voice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6816230416297913,
            "question": "Can you name any other characters voiced by Linda Ballantyne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6813008785247803,
            "question": "Is Linda Ballantyne a famous voice actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6370055675506592,
            "question": "What makes Percy the Small Engine a popular character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49502965807914734,
            "question": "What kind of media features Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4320979416370392,
            "question": "What is Linda Ballantyne known for voicing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.405060738325119,
            "question": "Has Linda Ballantyne won any awards for her voice acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09383893013000488,
            "question": "Do you know any other actors who have voiced characters in similar shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Percy the Small Engine is voiced by Linda Ballantyne.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4411_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Linda Ballantyne won any awards for her voice acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4411_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Linda Ballantyne known for voicing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4411_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of media features Percy the Small Engine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4411_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4411_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Percy is voiced by Linda Ballantyne\" and \"Percy in Thomas and the Magic Railroad[edit]... Percy is voiced by female actress Linda Ballantyne.\" This information supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "In the context information provided, it is stated that Percy was voiced by Linda Ballantyne in a movie (Thomas and the Magic Railroad), but in the later sections of the text, it is mentioned that Percy is typically voiced by Keith Wickham (2009-2015), Nigel Pilkington (2015-2021), and Christopher Ragland (2016; singing voice) in the television series. The discrepancy suggests that Linda Ballantyne is not the regular voice actor for Percy in the series, but only voiced him in a specific movie.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state Percy was voiced by Linda Ballantyne in the movie \"Thomas and the Magic Railroad\" but other voice actors are listed for later appearances in the series.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple instances where Linda Ballantyne is stated to be the voice actor for Percy, contradicting only one instance where a different voice actor (Keith Wickham) is mentioned.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided shows that Linda Ballantyne voiced Percy in the 2000 film \"Thomas and the Magic Railroad,\" but not necessarily in other productions. Additionally, it mentions that from 2016 to at least 2021, Christopher Ragland voiced Percy in some series.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}